# Satguru Saran Satsangi P.

Product Designer & UX Researcher

Website: http://psssatsangi.com/ Email: satsangi77@gmail.com

Phone: +13177021793

# Summary

I use research, creative intuition, and an arsenal of user-centered activities to uncover insights that define opportunities and support corporate objectives. I also strengthen relationships with internal and external partners through process and workflow development, project prioritization, planning and scoping efforts.

## **Experience**

### Design Researcher | Walmart

March 2019- Present

Bentonville, Arkansas

I am part of a serious UX team at Walmart Home office. I work as a hybrid finding opportunities and solutioning using UX Design and Research methods.

Product Designer | New Wisdom, LLC Indianapolis, Indiana

October 2017- December 2018

I worked as a designer for Augmented Reality projects. I won the best capstone project award from Indiana University. I also worked remotely for another project for which I collaborated with Dev. and 3D modeling teams from other countries.

## Graduate Research Assistant (UI/UX) | Indiana

January 2017- Dec 2018

#### University

Indianapolis, Indiana

I lead the UX team in COMET LAB. My key responsibilities include creating wireframes, prototyping, storyboarding and conducting qualitative and quantitative research.

## **UI/UX Designer | The Workshops**

June 2014- July 2014

Cairo, Egypt

I worked as a UX Designer for implementing a website for the NGO, which is used for training Egyptian women in different fields. My responsibilities include requirement gathering, designing wireframes and prototyping, Information Architecture, user testing and collaborating with the developer.

# Education

**MS Human Computer Interaction** Indiana University, Indianapolis January 2017 - December 2018

**B.Tech Information Technology** Gayatri Vidya Parishad College of Engineering August 2011 - May 2016

# Skills

## Design

Visual Design Story Boarding Wire-framing Interactive Prototyping Sketching Information Architecture

### Research Mothods

Affinity Mapping Heuristic Evaluation **Usability Testing** Focus Analysis Persona Cognitive Walkthrough A/B testing Contextual Inquiry Competitive Analysis **Card Sorting** 

# **Design Tools**

Adobe Creative Suit Sketch **InVision Figma** Marvel

# **Programming**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL

#### **Others**

Agile-Jira | leankit | Scrum Plant, Zeplin